Why does simmulation A appear to have a normal distrabution, but B does not?

In simulation B, if we randomly generate a number between 2 through 12 N times 
(where N is a large number), we should expect about the same probability for each
possible number (2 is just as likely to get as 8 for example). 

What about simulation A? In simulation A, we are generating two different numbers
and adding them together. What are the possible ways we could add two numbers 
between 1 and 6 to get 7? 1 & 6, 2 & 5, 3 & 4, 4 & 3, 5 & 2, and 6 & 1. That's 
six different ways. Now what about the possible ways to get 2? There is only one
way. That is to roll 1 & 1. What about 12? Likewise there is only one possibility.
This is where the normal distrabution comes from. The more possibilities to sum
up to a specific number, the more likely that sum will show up in the final result.

Thus we can see that even small details are important when trying to simulate an
event. 